FAHAD IFTIKHAR

FREELANCE WRITER



MORE ABOUT ME

A software engineering student with 1 year experience in writing and 2 years of experience developing software. I started my software engineering studies to further enhance my software knowledge along with following my hobby of creative writing.

GET IN TOUCH

Mobile: +92 3185145083 fhdiftkharegmail.com linkedin.com/in/fahad-iftikhar-b81391217 Bahria Town Phase 8, Rawalpindi, Punjab, Pakistan

CORE COMPETENCIES

Copywriting, Proposal Development, Presentations, Articles, Essays, Research, Resumes, Editing, Software Writing, Software Scripting, Usability Analysis, Vulnerability Testing, Software Development, Web Development

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

Outside of writing and reading, gaming, mountaineering, running, cooking, music, nature photography, Coding, blogging, and traveling.

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Freelance Writer

Based in Rawalpindi (July 2021- Present)

I provide writing services to various clients, businesses, and publications. What I do includes cover letters, summaries, articles, prompts, and more.

Marketing Analyst

Pompak (may 2021 - April 2022)

Helped Pompak, a software development company to boost their sales while maximizing profit and customer satisfaction. Boosted the software sales by 40% with marketing strategies.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Riphah International University

Bachelor of Computer Sciences (2021 - ongoing)
Member of Writing Club
Member of IEEE RIU society

Global College of Sciences

Intermediate in Computer Sciences 2021

Courses/Certifications

Python for Everybody (Coursera)
Decentralized Finance (Coursera)
Google Data Analytics (Google)
Meta Marketing Analytics (Meta)